{
    "id": "ee8e69d7e7f840b08681ea8ff82be3b1",
    "title": "So That",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He borrowed some money from his friend so that ......................... buy a car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "003d88806bad4ffa977e432c54ed5fda"
        },
        {
            "question": "We eat so that we .................... live.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "might",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "351dbe96679b4a24ba4206ce6f7e1425"
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked hard so that he ....................... pass the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "might",
                "could",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f2df990cede146e29ff592ed4543f298"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our team played well ..................... they could win the match.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "in order to",
                "so as to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f857ca0979394acea700757116937b03"
        },
        {
            "question": "They grew vegetables in the backyard so that they ........................ have fresh vegetables all year round.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "might",
                "can",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "30c0d70c8fd84df684ce995324684e68"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wrote the number on a piece of paper so that I ..................... forget it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "won't",
                "wouldn't",
                "couldn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e9d8b55138b54f82bd0e0a46ed8bcd26"
        },
        {
            "question": "He offered his daughter a prize so that she ....................... work hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "will",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b960844f6d4d4e9a9cc33a94b1f30b5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She stayed in London for six months so that she ........................ perfect her English.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "559c9e7407e34c00bc35f2b45513546f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have come early so that I ....................... talk to you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "will",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a70a3655bb134e69ba4fc4bb1d399aca"
        },
        {
            "question": "He left home early so that he .......................... get to the meeting in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7b0f8e38fd7434d95b455a22d23356b"
        }
    ]
}